message,clean_message,word_count,entities
"Phillip, I need the updated numbers for the energy trading meeting tomorrow. Let me know if you have them ready. - Ken Lay","phillip, i need the updated numbers for the energy trading meeting tomorrow. let me know if you have them ready. - ken lay",22,"[('Phillip', 'PERSON'), ('Ken Lay', 'PERSON'), ('tomorrow', 'DATE')]"
"Jeff, the LJM transaction needs final approval from the board. Please review the documents. - Andrew Fastow","jeff, the ljm transaction needs final approval from the board. please review the documents. - andrew fastow",18,"[('Jeff', 'PERSON'), ('LJM', 'ORG'), ('Andrew Fastow', 'PERSON')]"
The regulatory committee is meeting in Houston next week to discuss California power markets. - Greg Whalley,the regulatory committee is meeting in houston next week to discuss california power markets. - greg whalley,16,"[('Houston', 'GPE'), ('next week', 'DATE'), ('California', 'GPE'), ('Greg Whalley', 'PERSON')]"
Lunch with Vince Kaminski today to discuss risk management models. - Phillip Allen,lunch with vince kaminski today to discuss risk management models. - phillip allen,12,"[('Vince Kaminski', 'PERSON'), ('today', 'DATE'), ('Phillip Allen', 'PERSON')]"
Enron North America is leading the pack in online trading volumes this quarter. Great job everyone.,enron north america is leading the pack in online trading volumes this quarter. great job everyone.,16,"[('Enron North America', 'ORG'), ('this quarter', 'DATE')]"
"Sally, please send the contract details for the Portland General Electric deal. - Phillip Allen","sally, please send the contract details for the portland general electric deal. - phillip allen",16,"[('Sally', 'PERSON'), ('Portland General Electric', 'ORG'), ('Phillip Allen', 'PERSON')]"
The weather forecast in the Northeast suggests high demand for natural gas. We should adjust our positions. - John Lavorato,the weather forecast in the northeast suggests high demand for natural gas. we should adjust our positions. - john lavorato,19,"[('Northeast', 'LOC'), ('natural gas', 'PRODUCT'), ('John Lavorato', 'PERSON')]"
Meeting scheduled with the FERC representatives in Washington D.C. next Tuesday regarding the supply chain. - Steven Kean,meeting scheduled with the ferc representatives in washington d.c. next tuesday regarding the supply chain. - steven kean,17,"[('FERC', 'ORG'), ('Washington D.C.', 'GPE'), ('next Tuesday', 'DATE'), ('Steven Kean', 'PERSON')]"
The broadband division is showing promising growth in the new data center in Las Vegas. - Ken Rice,the broadband division is showing promising growth in the new data center in las vegas. - ken rice,17,"[('Las Vegas', 'GPE'), ('Ken Rice', 'PERSON')]"
Legal review of the Raptor entities is complete. We are good to proceed with the hedging strategy.,legal review of the raptor entities is complete. we are good to proceed with the hedging strategy.,17,"[('Raptor', 'ORG')]"
